Guide to the Victor Remer Historical Archives of the Children's Aid Society 1836-2006 (bulk 1853-1947) MS 111
New-York Historical Society
- Series III - Reports, 1853-2006 (bulk 1853-1942)
  - Subseries III.1 - Annual Reports, 1854-2006
    - 96th Annual Report, "The New Crop" (3), 1948 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 10)
    - 97th Annual Report, "Cheaper By the Dozen" (2), 1949 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 11)
    - 98th Annual Report, "Children Must Be Ready" (2), 1950 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 12)
    - 99th Annual Report, "More Young Children, More Needs, More Care" (2), 1951 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 13)
    - 100th Annual Report, "Report of the Hundredth Year" (1), 1952 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 14)
    - 101st Annual Report, "Another Century - A Record and a Promise" (2), 1953 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 15)
    - 102nd Annual Report, "The City is the Children" (2), 1954 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 16)
    - 103rd Annual Report, "Special Interest - Children" (2), 1955 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 17)
    - 104th Annual Report, "Tomorrow's Children" (2), 1956 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 18)
    - 105th Annual Report, "What About the 99 Per Cent?" (2), 1957 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 19)
    - 106th Annual Report, "Growing to Meet Their Needs" (2), 1958 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 20)
    - 107th Annual Report, "Children Must Choose" (2), 1959 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 21)
    - 108th Annual Report, "The Right Place...at the Right Time" (2), 1960 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 22)
    - 109th Annual Report, "Children are the Future" (2), 1961 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 23)
    - 110th Annual Report, "Children Unlimited" (2), 1962 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
    - 111th Annual Report, "These Are Your Children" (2), 1963 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
    - 112th Annual Report (1), 1964 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report (2), 1965 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report (2 formats, 2 copies of each), 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report (2 formats, 2 copies of each), 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report (1), 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report (1), 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report (2), 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, Vol. 2, No. 2 (2), 1972 Fall (Offsite-box 10, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report (2), 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report (2), 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report (2), 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report (2), 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report (2), 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report (1), 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report (2), 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report (2), 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report (2), 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report (2), 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report (2), 1983 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report (2), 1984 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report (2), 1985 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 23)
    - Annual Report (2), 1986 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 24)
    - Annual Report (2), 1987 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 25)
    - Annual Report (2), 1988 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 26)
    - Annual Report (2), 1989 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 27)
    - Annual Report (2), 1990 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 28)
    - Annual Report, "Forever Young - Partnerships for the Future" (2), 1991 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 29)
    - Annual Report (2), 1993 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, "To Be a Child" (2), 1994 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, "Letters From Our Children" (2), 1995 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report (2), 1996 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, "Our World" (2), 1997 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, "We're Everywhere You Look" (2), 1998 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, "The Spirit of the Child - Our Mission and Relevance in the 21st Century" (2), 1999 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, "Service + Advocacy = Change" (2), 2000 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, "On the Front Lines of Change" (2), 2001 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, "An Enduring Mission in Times of Change" (2), 2002 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, "Children's Services Today and Tomorrow" (1), 2003 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, "Growing Up Healthy" (2), 2004 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, "Rising to the Challenge" (2), 2005 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, "The Need to Succeed: Teens Chart Their Course" (2), 2006 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 13)
  - Subseries III.2 - Reports, Articles, and Addresses for the Public and Particular Audiences, 1857-1942
    Subseries III.2 contains reports other than the Annual Reports, as well as other types of articles and presentations composed for the public, or for smaller audiences. The materials range in form, from reports bound in larger booklets, to short reports in the form of informational pamphlets, to letters to the editor, to typescripts of papers, public addresses and radio speeches. Some of the material is in draft form. The materials in this subseries were created to inform the public (or particular smaller audiences) about social issues of concern to the Children's Aid Society, to promote the Children's Aid Society's solutions, and indirectly to encourage donations or other support. The subseries spans the years 1857-circa 1942. Arranged chronologically, this subseries provides a good overview of the shifting concerns of the CAS over the years.
    See also the published works of Charles Loring Brace (Series IV, volumes 39-42) and the booklets and pamphlets in Series VI.3 (Fund-Raising Materials) for other reports composed for the public. See also Series VII for reports on legal matters, Series IX for reports on facilities, Series X for reports on medical programs, Series XI for reports on the Emigration and Foster Home Programs, and Series XII for reports on other programs.
    Note: This subseries contains reports by two people named Charles Loring Brace. Founder Charles Loring Brace is identified by that name in this collection. His son, who followed him as Secretary of CAS in 1890 and went by the same name or by C. Loring Brace or Loring Brace or C.L. Brace, is identified as Charles Loring Brace II for the purposes of this collection.
    - "Address Upon the Industrial School Movement, Delivered at a Union Meeting of the Ladies of the Industrial Schools," by Charles Loring Brace, 1857 November (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    - "The Best Method of Disposing of Our Pauper and Vagrant Children," by Charles Loring Brace, 1859 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - "The Cost of a Charity" Analysis of 1873 CAS expenses, justifying expenditures to potential donors, by Charles Loring Brace, 1874 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    - "Some Reasons Why," a report in defense of public funding of CAS Industrial Schools, author unknown, typescript, circa 1875-1925 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    - "Summer Charities of the Children's Aid Society," by G. Calder, Superintendent, 1881 May 20 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    - "Child Saving as Shown in Summer Homes and Sanitaria Near Large Cities," a Paper Presented to the National Conference of Charities, by Charles Loring Brace, 1884 October 15 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    - "Dutch Hill, a Picture of the N.Y. Poor," an early article describing conditions and soliciting donations for an Industrial School, by Charles Loring Brace, undated, before 1890 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
    - Photocopies of 6 Articles by Charles Loring Brace II: "How Boys Come to be Bad" (1892), "Child Life on the Streets" (1894), "Reply from CAS" (1899), "A Work of Practical Benevolence" (1901), "The Children of the Poor in Great Cities" (1902), and "Truancy" (1906), 1892, 1894, 1899, 1901, 1902, 1906 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
    - League for Social Service Pamphlet Series G: "Children's Aid Society of NY," by Charles Loring Brace II, 1898 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
    - Letter to the Editor of Charities, by Charles Loring Brace II, 1899 December 23 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 10)
    - "The Salary Question" [by A.B. Hepburn, Treasurer], typescript, 1899 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
    - Children's Aid Society Statement of Purpose [by William Church Osborn, President], typescript, circa 1902-1907 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12)
    - "Improvement in Philanthropic Methods," paper by Charles Loring Brace II, typescript, 1904 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 13)
    - "Education of Cripples and Mentally Deficient Children in their Own Homes," paper by Charles Loring Brace II, typescript, 1905 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 14)
    - "Child Saving," a paper prepared for the International Congress of Public and Private Charities, Milan, Italy, by Charles Loring Brace II, typescript, 1906 May 23-27 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 15)
    - "The Emigration of Homeless Children to the Country" aka "The Children's Aid Society of New York: Its Emigration or Placing Out System and its Results" - CAS author(s) unknown, bound report, 1910 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 16)
    - Address at the Roosevelt Luncheon, by Charles Loring Brace II, 1911 May 5 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 17)
    - "The Industrial Schools of the Children's Aid Society of New York City," by A. Blair Thaw, M.D., founder of the Sixty-fourth Street Industrial School, later merged with the Henrietta School, bound report, 1911 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 18)
    - "The Children's Aid Society of New York in its Seventieth Year," by Charles Loring Brace II, 1923 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 19)
    - "Why Should I Give?" by C.R. Conklin, CAS Medical Director, Reprinted from Hospital Social Service XII, 1925, 158 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 20)
    - Report on Nutritional Work Carried Out by the CAS, small booklet published by CAS (2 copies), 1926 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 21)
    - "The Crusade for Children 1853-1928," bound report (see also Annual Report 1927) (Offsite-box 12, Folder 22)
    - "New York Child-Life in 1929," by Owen Lovejoy, bound report (Offsite-box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Mending Broken Homes: a Report of the Work of the Department of Family Homes" (bound report, 2 copies including 1 annotated by unknown person), 1929 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 24)
    - Letter to the Editor of the New York Times, on Horatio Alger, the Newsboys' Lodging House, and Brace and Bowdoin Farms, by Owen Lovejoy, typescript, 1932 January (Offsite-box 12, Folder 25)
    - "The Negro Children of New York," by Owen Lovejoy, bound report, 1932 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 26)
    - A series of 8 CAS radio addresses on the problem of homeless boys, delivered weekly by celebrated people, including Eleanor Roosevelt, Alfred E. Smith, and others, typescripts, 1932 November 29-1933 January 17 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 27)
    - "America's Wandering Boys," by Owen Lovejoy, article printed in Current History, 1933 February (Offsite-box 12, Folder 28)
    - "Bowdoin Farm" by unknown CAS author, typescript draft of speech or report, 1933 August 7 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 29)
    - "Radio Talk" by unknown CAS author, typescript, 1933 October 16 and 1934 January 5 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 30)
    - "As the Twig is Bent" by unknown CAS author, typescript draft of a speech on homeless boys, circa 1933 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 31)
    - Radio Speech on Homeless Boys, unknown CAS author, broadcast on Station WGNY, Chester NY, typescript copy, 23 July 1935 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 32)
    - Radio Speech on Bowdoin Farm, typescript draft with corrections, circa 1935 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 33)
    - Two Radio Programs on Bowdoin Farm (typescripts) and related correspondence between Margaret M. Fellows and Mahlon N. Champlin, 1936 November 24-1937 May 8 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 34)
    - "The Youth of the Future and the Future of Youth" by William Church Osborn, radio address, typescript, circa 1935 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 35)
    - 3 Reports by unknown CAS authors: "The CAS' Work for Homeless and Transient Boys" (photocopy), untitled article from Tribune on same subject (typescript, incomplete), and "Back to the Land" on the same subject (photocopy of a draft article for Rural New Yorker), 1938 March, 1938 April, and undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 36)
    - Transcription of promotional film made for CAS, "The Disinherited," and related correspondence, 1939 May 5-1940 August 9 and undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 37)
    - Addresses delivered by William Church Osborn and Hon. Alfred A. Smith at a program of films about the CAS at the Museum of Modern Art, typescript, 1940 February 6 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 38)
    - Untitled Essay by William Church Osborn, typescript, 1940 March 21 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 39)
    - "Youth and Opportunity," by William Church Osborn, typescript, 1940 August (Offsite-box 12, Folder 40)
    - "Who Will Milk the Cow and Do the Chores?" by Margaret M. Fellows, article published in Land Policy Review Vol. IV, No. 5, photocopy of published article and typescript draft of same, 1941 May (Offsite-box 12, Folder 41)
    - "For Every Child...A Home," by the Homeless Children's Committee of the CAS, bound report, 1941 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 42)
    - "Children in Wartime" regarding CAS preparedness and programs in WWII, pamphlet, circa 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 43)
  - Subseries III.3 - Reports to Supervisory Agencies and Other Organizations, 1873-1937
    Subseries III.3 contains reports to supervisory agencies, written in fulfillment of annual requirements, and reports to other organizations. The subseries is divided into 4 sub-subseries, each arranged chronologically.
    III.3.A contains Reports to the State Board of Charities 1873-1929 (missing 1874-1876, 1878-1880, 1896, and 1919-1921).
    III.3.B contains Reports to the State Department of Social Welfare (the subsequent name for the State Board of Charities, and a continuation of the reports in the previous sub-subseries) 1930-1937. The reports in the first two subseries give a thorough statistical accounting of the work of the Children's Aid Society.
    III.3.C contains Reports to the New York City Department of Finance 1920, 1921, and 1926.
    III.3.D contains two other reports: a Report to the Council of the Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor 1923, and a Report to the Trustees of Mrs. Kane's Estate, "Supervised Playgrounds," requesting allocation of funds for a self-supporting girl's club and apartment (circa 1927).
    - Sub-Subseries III.3.A - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1873-1929
      - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1873, 1877 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
      - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1881, 1882, 1883 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
      - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1884, 1885, 1886 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
      - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
      - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1890, 1891, 1892 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
      - Reports to the State Board of Charities, 1893, 1894, 1895 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1897 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1898 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1899 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1900 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1901 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1902 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 12)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1903 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 13)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1904 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1905 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1906 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1907 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1908 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1909 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1910 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1911 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1912 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1913 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1914 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1915 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1916 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1917 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1918 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1922 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1923 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1924 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1925 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1926 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1927 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1928 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
      - Report to the State Board of Charities, 1929 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    - Sub-Subseries III.3.B - Reports to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1930-1937
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1930 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1932 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 9)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 10)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1934 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 11)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1935 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 12)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1936 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 13)
      - Report to the State Department of Social Welfare, 1937 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 14)
    - Sub-Subseries III.3.C - Reports to the New York City Department of Finance, 1920-1926
      - Report to the New York City Department of Finance, 1920 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 15)
      - Report to the New York City Department of Finance, 1921 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 16)
      - Report to the New York City Department of Finance, 1926 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 17)
    - Sub-Subseries III.3.D - Other Reports, 1923 and circa 1927
      - Report to the Council of the Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor, 1923 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
      - Report to the Trustees of Mrs. Kane's Estate: "Supervised Playgrounds", circa 1927 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
  - Subseries III.4 - Internal Reports, 1853-1921
    Subseries 4 consists of 5 reports written presumably for a CAS internal audience (Board of Trustees or other). The reports in this small subseries cover a range of topics, dated 1853-circa 1921. For other internal reports related to individual facilities or programs of the CAS, see materials corresponding to those programs in Series IX-XI, or for legal reports see Series VII.
    - Statistics of Immorality and Crime in the 4th Ward, by E.J. Gerry, CAS, 1853 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    - "The Fresh Air Charities" by CAS Fresh Air Committee (Board of Trustees) - History and Suggestions for Future Direction, circa 1886-1900 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    - Joint Report of the Commitees of the Five Points House of Industry and the Children's Aid Society on the care of Dependent Committed Children, delivered to the Trustees, draft typescript, incomplete (note: many children in the CAS emigration program came first through Five Points House of Industry, and the two organizations shared board members including William Church Osborn, William Wheelock, and Morris Jessup. From 1909-circa 1919 the two organizations merged, and CAS' Italian School rented space in the Five Points House of Industry building.), circa 1909 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Italian Immigrant: Is He Ambitious, Moral and Able?" by unknown CAS author [Mrs. Weygandt, Principal of Italian School?], undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - Report on Astor Family Contributions to CAS 1853-1921 (photocopy), circa 1921 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III.5 - Reports Produced Outside the Auspices of CAS, 1895-1941
    Subseries III.5 consists of 14 reports and speeches, 1895-1941, produced outside the auspices of CAS, but concerning the CAS mission. Several of these reports were written by people associated with CAS, but not writing as representatives of the agency. Most reports in the series were written by people unconnected to CAS, but the documents were saved and kept by people in the CAS who considered them relevant.
    - "Fresh Air Work in New York City" by William H. Tolman, Ph.D., 1895 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - "For the Milan Congress. 5th Question" [on social insurance] by Professor C.R. Henderson, University of Chicago, 1906 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 9)
    - Excerpt from Draft Report: "The Evolution of the Child-Placing Movement" by Hastings H. Hart, and the program from the conference at which the report was delivered, 1909 January 25 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Report of the Babies' Welfare Association, with focus on the Children's Aid Society, by Garret Smith, 1914 June 6 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 11)
    - "Report of Work done by the Department of Public Charities for Babies Proposed for Commitment July and August 1915" and "A Study of the Care of Babies Committed by the Department of Public Charities of the City of New York to the New York Nursery and Childs' Hospital June 1915" and "Memorandum to the Second Deputy Commissioner - Suggestive Criticism of Methods Employed in Dealing with Applications July and August 1915" - Disbound typescripts of reports by William J. Doherty, circa 1915 September (Offsite-box 17, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Report of the Babies' Welfare Association, Department of Health, City of NY, Vol. 3, No. 22 (includes notice of CAS Health Home at Coney Island), 1917 June 9 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Study of Children's Aid Society Property in Manhattan to Determine its Availability and Adaptability for Boys' Club Purposes" prepared by Boys' Club Federation, includes analysis of neighborhoods, delinquency, and architectural drawings, 1928 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 14)
    - "Minimum Standards for Convalescent Homes" published by the Welfare Council (Dr. Charles Conklin, CAS Medical Director, on committee. Folder includes a letter by him explaining reason for report), 1895 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 15)
    - "Some Problems of Convalescence" by Charles R. Conklin, Medical Director of CAS, chapter from unknown anthology of reports, circa 1925-1930 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 16)
    - "Newsboys of New York: A Study of Their Legal and Illegal Work Activities During 1931" by Harry M. Shulman, New York Child Labor Committee (Owen Lovejoy, Secretary of CAS, was at the same time Chairman of the NYCLC, which operated out of the United Charities Building, as did CAS.), 1932 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 17)
    - "The Story of the United Charities Building: Mr. John S. Kennedy's Relation to the Building and His Policies Regarding It" by Robert W. De Forest, 1936 abridgement of a 1931 Report, and 2 related photocopies (Offsite-box 17, Folder 18)
    - "Where Do We Go From Here?" By William Church Osborn, Vice President of the Citizens Budget Commission (Osborn was also President of CAS 1902-1949), 1941 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 19)